FILING FOR LOVE
SENDER: NONAME
TITLE: REPORTING MS. JOO IN-A
SHE IS INVOLVED IN AN INAPPROPRIATE
WORKPLACE RELATIONSHIP
HIDE SENDER ID
TITLE: REPORTING MS. JOO IN-A
SHE IS INVOLVED IN
AN INAPPROPRIATE...
SEND
EMAIL WAS SENT SUCCESSFULLY
MS. JOO IN-A
...AN INAPPROPRIATE
WORKPLACE RELATIONSHIP
HAEMU STRATEGIC PLANNING, MARKETING,
DIGITAL MARKETING, AUDIT TEAM 1, 2, 3
SEND
SECRETARY AHN SEUNG-HEE
- Hey.
- A-jeong.
Check out the article I just sent.
HAEMU'S FIRSTBORN DRIVEN OUT?
SIBLING RIVALRY HEATS UP
Did you call the PR Team?
Look into the journalist
and find out how he got the story.
I'll call Legal.
In-a.
Can I help you?
I'm cleaning the suite.
You can't...
You're gonna burn a hole
through my face.
I know I'm a charming
and good-looking guy, but...
What are you doing?
Checking to see if you're real.
How did you manage to show up
right at that moment?
Unbelievable.
What kind of moment was it?
It was the moment I thought
that I wanted to see you.
How could you say something
so heart-fluttering
with such a straight face?
I was regretting
not being true to my feelings.
I wanted to turn things back
but thought it was too late.
I was upset,
and it left me with regrets.
But at the same time, I thought
"Oh, I'd love to see
Ki-jun right now."
Just when I was thinking that,
you appeared out of nowhere.
I kind of knew that feeling
so I rushed here
without wasting a second.
Thank you for coming to get me.
Let's turn things back one by one.
I won't go to the US.
I'm doing whatever it takes to stay.
If you try to force me to go
I'll lie down flat in the lobby
to protest so I can stay.
The thing is, going to the US office
would be a great opportunity for you.
Didn't we agree to be honest?
Should I actually go?
No, don't go.
Stay right next to me.
You bet.
- That's it?
- Yes, that's it.
What about the other side?
What's this?
We only just said goodbye.
Do you miss me already?
Yes, I miss you.
My heart almost burst.
Over that?
You should brace yourself.
Once I start dating someone
I get all passionate and fired up.
I knew it.
I should brace myself
to date someone like you.
I'm not so easygoing either.
So you should brace yourself as well.
What, really?
What should I prepare first?
Why don't we figure out
what to call each other?
I don't want
to have to call you "Ms. Joo."
It's too formal and unfriendly.
My darling In-a.
In-a.
Now that I think about it
you have a beautiful name.
Joo In-a.
- Hi, guys.
- Hey.
- Let's drink.
- Cheers.
Jae-yeol, what's up with you?
You never joined us
when we invited you before.
I know I was too distant.
Sorry about that.
Hey, I think you should slow down.
Aren't you drinking too much?
Are you getting wasted because
your stepbrother was made co-VP?
I read about that in the news.
Your father's just...
He could've just put things in order
instead of making him co-VP.
It's like he put you two
in a cage to fight.
You talk too much
when we're here to drink.
- Drink up.
- Yes.
Jae-yeol rarely joins us for drinks.
- Let's drink.
- And get wasted.
It's cold, isn't it?
No.
Do you like it that much?
Yes.
I can't believe I look forward
to going to work in the morning.
For real?
I love heading into work.
Work is much more fun
than being bored at home.
No wonder.
You had a look of madness
in your eyes.
We'll do more fun things together
other than just work.
Clear your schedule this weekend.
We went all the way to Jeju Island
but had to return right away.
I booked a pool villa in Sokcho.
Let's take our time
to play in the sea
and get some fresh air.
Is this an overnight trip?
It's... Well...
A one-day trip
won't leave us much time.
I love it.
I'm kind of worried
that I won't be able to hide
how much I like you at work.
- What should I do?
- I'd love to see that.
Not being able to hide it.
Don't smile like that.
If you smile, I can't help but smile,
and my feelings will show.
This is a serious matter.
It's going to be too obvious.
Too obvious, my foot.
Even when she's in a relationship
Joo In-a was
still her old self at work.
So what is your conclusion?
It doesn't say on this page
or on this page.
There's nothing.
This report has no key point!
See this?
Do you see a key point
in this report?
This is the kind of report you should
pay to write, not be paid to write.
It's a waste of paper.
Rewrite the whole thing.
Are you all right, Mr. Noh?
Mr. Noh.
Did you do something
to get on her nerves?
No, it's because he's working
too much.
Mr. Noh, be more like me.
Talk more and do less.
The more an auditor does,
the harder they get audited.
The more you do,
the more there is to criticize.
Those are such wise words.
For someone who doesn't do much
how do you end up with the most
overtime pay each month?
Will you all stop it?
Ms. Yoon.
Did you finish the slides
for the presentation on our clubs?
Yes, I emailed you the final version.
Good job.
Did you add as many photos, tables,
and animations as possible?
I'm sure you did your job.
Good for you.
When we present the report
to Ms. Joo later
you're all coming with me.
You, too, Mr. Noh.
Ms. Joo is a really nice person.
Don't be too afraid of her.
Okay.
I'm sure she's a nice person.
The problem is that she's too nice.
Ms. Park?
- Yes?
- When will VP Jeon be here?
He isn't well today.
I'll present the agenda instead.
Okay.
We can't wait forever.
Let's start without him.
Don't you forget
that I am a VP as well.
Yes, I think
it would be fine to start.
Ms. Park, you can leave.
- But...
- Being a secretary
doesn't give you the right
to attend in a VP's place.
VICE PRESIDENT
SECRETARY PARK A-JEONG
- Gosh, the water...
- It's so clear.
Were they rockfish? Did you see them?
- Yes.
- There was a swarm.
- It was amazing.
- Just fantastic.
- Did you notice?
- Yes.
- Right?
- Did you?
- I saw.
- What was that?
It was incredible.
The water's so clear today.
- It's a rare occasion.
- I know.
- You're back.
- Yes.
Did you have fun?
Is Seo-yeon in bed?
Yes.
Her English kindergarten is hosting
a cooking class on the 29th.
You can make it, right?
- I have a club meeting on the 29th.
- Again?
Why do you have to go
scuba diving that often?
Can't you miss it for once?
I went on my own
to Seo-yeon's speech contest.
Do you know how upset she was
that you'd missed it?
I'll be at the next one.
Are you sure you go scuba diving?
Are you up to something else?
AUDIT SUMMARY
We found four cases in which
clubs fraudulently enrolled
new recruits or temporary staff
to collect extra club funds.
And in seven cases,
club admin embezzled club funds
rented spaces or paid instructors
for personal gain.
We found eight malpractice cases
where club members
hired businesses
run by friends or family.
In two cases, there were issues
that constituted gambling.
The in-house clubs currently hand in
- an activity report yearly, right?
- Yes, that's right.
Have them submit one each quarter
with more details in the report.
Ask HR to make the announcement.
Okay, I'll relay the message.
We also have a club-related PM case.
The wife of Min Tae-woo
at Haemu International contacted us.
Her husband is way too active
in the scuba diving club.
She's not entirely sure
their activities are wholesome.
It's hard to tell because of the gear
but the man on the right is Mr. Min.
The person on the right is
suspected to be his affair partner.
The wife found many photos
of this person in particular.
Aren't they just enjoying a hobby?
It did seem somewhat odd.
Mr. Min supposedly dislikes water
and didn't even swim.
He goes scuba diving
almost every week now.
He's known to even
take time off work to go.
And at home,
he always says he's tired.
Oh, and he gets calls at dawn
or in the middle of the night
and jumps up to go out.
Many complain
that company clubs foster affairs
and that the company encourages it
by covering expenses.
Why don't we make this an example
and look into this incident?
We won't get anywhere
with what we have if they deny it.
Let's attend a club outing
and see how things actually are.
Mr. Noh.
Do you know how to scuba-dive?
I did take a few lessons
on a trip once.
You should go to Mr. Min's club
- this weekend.
- What?
This weekend
I have an important appointment.
Do you?
Is anyone else able to scuba-dive?
Extended exposure to water
gives me a rash.
- The sea...
- That's bad.
I almost drowned in a river
as a child and the trauma...
- I can't equalize underwater.
- I can't manage.
I refuse to work on weekends.
It verges on a rare disease.
Oh, dear...
I'm left with no choice, then.
I love scuba diving.
- I'll go.
- What?
What?
Don't you have anything planned
for this weekend?
I don't have
any special plans this weekend.
Clear your schedule this weekend.
I booked a pool villa in Sokcho.
I thought I didn't have plans.
You do have plans, then.
How could you?
Aren't you happy
we get to travel together?
We're doing
exactly what we planned to do.
We see the sea
and get some fresh air.
- Plus, we get to work, too.
- Goodness.
We hit two birds with one stone
by going swimming
and seeing some fish.
You said you get passionate
when you start dating.
But all you did was
make me work passionately.
I thought I was going
to burn to ashes with your passion.
That was because we had a lot to do
because of the previous week's trip.
Also, I didn't want anyone at work
to notice anything.
I put on an act with a poker face.
You got so into that act
that you forgot our weekend plan.
That was because it's been so long
since I made weekend plans.
Plus, this is work.
I'm very good at separating
work from my personal life.
Yes, of course. I get it, Ms. Joo.
We're on a business trip,
not a pleasure cruise.
I'll make sure to act accordingly,
completely aloof and official.
Ki-jun, are you actually angry?
Yes.
You fool. You twit.
How could you forget your first date?
- Get a grip, In-a!
- Don't.
- What are you doing?
- What?
I deserve a good scolding.
- You fool. You twit. You moron.
- No, stop it. Don't do that.
I was kidding, okay?
I'm not angry at all. I was joking.
- You seemed really angry.
- I wasn't.
I wasn't even sulking.
I'm really sorry.
Don't be.
Goodness...
We have new members joining us today.
It's Ms. Joo In-a, Head of Audit
from the head office
and Assistant Manager Noh Ki-jun.
- It's a pleasure to meet you all.
- Applause.
You're both from the Audit Team
so I feel somewhat nervous.
We use our funds appropriately
and we do nothing wrong, do we?
- Do you all agree?
- Yes.
Club president, don't you know
saying that makes you look guilty?
You have a point.
We have a small group today,
so we'll go out together.
Check your equipment thoroughly.
- Okay.
Get to it.
Hey.
Watch out.
This valve here needs to be checked.
We run on a buddy system.
This is your first dive with us
so you should partner
with someone more experienced.
I will partner with Mr. Min, then.
The way he's helping her
looks reliable and reassuring.
Then Mr. Min, you'll go out with him.
- Okay.
- Ms. Joo, your partner...
I volunteer.
Mr. Min and Ms. Ha seem pretty close.
Yes, they do.
Are you upset Ms. Ha
is his possible fling?
What?
You couldn't seem to take
your eyes off her.
What does that mean work-wise?
My eyes were not locked onto her.
It's all work-related.
I just wanted to confirm if she was
the other person in the photos.
I'll see you later.
Personal-wise.
Gosh...
Get ready to dive.
Get your equipment.
- Okay.
Be sure to check that.
- Okay, checked.
- Good.
- It's all done.
- Great.
Are you all right?
That seemed like a panic attack.
Are you claustrophobic or something?
I'm fine. It wasn't anything serious.
Did you tell the instructor?
You should inform the others
for their safety, too.
It's not that serious, okay?
Are you afraid you won't get to dive
if the others find out about this?
Do you love to dive that much?
You say too much
for someone who just joined.
I can handle my business.
Stay out of it.
Oh, come on.
It was a great dive.
He braves panic attacks to dive
just so he can see a woman regularly?
He could if he likes her that much.
It makes for a good excuse
for them to spend time together.
Ms. Ha is a veteran diver.
This story makes more sense.
Mr. Min fell for Ms. Ha first
found out what her hobby was,
and joined the club.
Gosh, if that's true
he's risking his life
for just an affair.
I'm so sorry about this.
I'd love to join you for dinner
but I have to get back to attend
an old coworker's father's funeral.
I had a great time today.
See you on the next dive.
- Goodbye.
- Get back safely.
- Bye.
- Sleep well.
- Goodbye.
What do we eat for dinner?
We had so much fun
swimming with the fish.
We're not eating raw fish, are we?
How about a toast?
- Good dive!
- Cheers.
They were friends only moments ago.
Goodbye, little fishies.
Ms. Joo is hilarious.
Don't you think?
These aren't the fish we saw,
so there's no need to feel bad.
The ssamjang here is the best.
Here we go. Open up.
Is it good?
Mr. Noh, you, too. Open up.
- What?
- Don't be shy.
Open your mouth wide.
That tastes amazing.
Ms. Ha, your wraps are the best.
Who taught you the recipe?
It's so good.
He drank enough alcohol
to kill himself.
If you were any later
something terrible could've happened.
That's not going to happen.
We can't go back
to how things used to be.
What I'm trying to say is
I'm never going back to you,
Jae-yeol.
OUR DEEPEST CONDOLENCES
MAY HE REST IN PEACE
Are you recruitment peers
with Mr. Lee, then?
He's one of the few guys
from the same batch.
Right. You realize
that when you're at work
your recruitment peer is
the closest you have to a friend.
All my peers retired early
- and recently, one...
- Mr. Han.
- Long time no see.
- Hi, take a seat.
- Hello.
- Let me introduce him, Mr. Moo.
This is Yoon Sang-ho from Haemu
International Global Business Team.
This is Audit Team's Leader
Moo Kwang-il.
- It's a pleasure.
- Same here.
I met two others
from your team today.
I just got back
from the Scuba Diving Club
and your head Ms. Joo
and Mr. Noh were there.
- Oh, I see.
- Yes.
- Let me pour you one.
- No, I drove here.
- I'll pour you one instead.
- What a pity.
- Not at all.
- Didn't you drive here
- if you just got back from a trip?
- I can always hire a driver.
- It's an honor to meet you.
- Same here.
What's up with Ms. Ha?
She stuck close to Mr. Min
but then
she seemed interested in you, too.
Well, I'm usually at the center
of everyone's attention.
Is she the type who wants to get
all the men's attention?
It's not all men, but me.
It's because I'm Noh Ki-jun.
It's Min and Ha.
He's loading her equipment
into his car, isn't he?
Something's up with them.
Wait.
Is he driving off with the equipment?
Yes.
It looks like Mr. Min
got a call from someone.
Where's Ms. Ha?
I'm really sorry.
I get carsick easily
and can't sit in the back.
Plus, that's usually
where the boss sits, right?
You're the boss.
I appreciate that.
By the way...
Where do you live, Mr. Noh?
- What?
- Do you live nearby?
I hope you don't have to make
too long a detour.
I don't. It's fine.
I have a question.
Don't you dislike joining a club
with your direct superior?
Oh, gosh. I can hear every word.
My bad.
Our dear Mr. Min's having a hard time
because his superior Mr. Yoon
is in the same club.
You and Mr. Min must be really close.
You talked so much earlier today
and just now you called him
"our dear Mr. Min."
Oh, gosh.
You got the wrong idea.
Mr. Min's married with a kid.
We're second cousins.
It's a pure coincidence
that we joined the same club.
Then you and Mr. Min
are just relatives?
Yes, that's why I loaded
my equipment in his trunk.
Wait, what? Are you serious?
Where did you get that idea?
Hey, you must
be working out, Mr. Noh.
Gosh, that's just hilarious.
I almost got the wrong idea
about you two.
It's so funny how things may seem.
Goodness...
So in the end, that new recruit
raided HR and made a huge fuss,
which resulted in
kicking out Mr. Lee
to another branch.
These days,
people call everything gaslighting.
We can't even talk anymore.
These kids only learned
the worst in everything.
I'm sure there was a situation...
It doesn't matter
what the situation is.
How dare some rookie dare
to kick the department head out?
How can this happen?
Mr. Moo, if this happened in the army
it'd be like a private messing
with the division commander. Jeez.
Well, the office
isn't the same as the army.
I mean, are they any different?
They're both organizations,
and there are ranks.
If so, we must also establish
proper discipline.
That's what I'm trying to say.
I thought you'd be more open-minded
because you're called the Global Team
but you're even more old-fashioned
than a Korean Audit Team.
Well, old-fashioned?
When we have team dinners,
we don't even drink regular soju.
We only get the red caps,
the ones with more alcohol content.
Goodness, look at the time.
- Please excuse me. Okay?
- You're leaving?
Yes, I'll leave
after saying goodbye to Mr. Lee.
- Eat up, then.
- Thanks.
- Goodbye.
- Hello.
- At our club today...
I told you to learn
how to scuba dive, didn't I?
I became acquainted
with the famous Head of Audit
Joo In-a, and met everyone.
I'll introduce her to you soon.
Mr. Moo isn't too resourceful.
There's no way
he's becoming an executive.
But he's a good man.
My friend, there's no use
in living as a good man.
Anyway, one second.
Hey, did you arrive?
Yes, okay. Come to the car. Okay.
- Sorry, my chauffeur's here.
- Okay. Bye.
Jeez. It was awful to listen to him
badmouth people for hours.
Wait. That's...
That's Mr. Min
from the Scuba Diving Club.
Is he waiting for someone?
What?
The chauffeur service Mr. Yoon called
was actually Mr. Min?
Not a hire?
Goodness, that guy.
See? I knew it the moment
he badmouthed those people.
What an awful man.
Mr. Noh, it's me.
I'm calling
about Mr. Yoon of the Global Team.
He's an awful man.
Mr. Yoon.
- Mr. Yoon.
- Man.
I had too much to drink.
One moment.
Gosh.
- I got it.
- Yes, sir.
- And the key. One second.
- Right.
You should have this hangover cure.
Man, that's my Native Speaker.
You're right on.
- Native Speaker.
- Yes, sir.
I've got your back until the very end
so just trust and follow me.
You know I'm the only one who
looks after you in the office, right?
Yes, of course.
I'm always grateful for you.
- Give me. And go.
- Yes, sir.
Mr. Yoon.
Well...
About the diving schedule
next Saturday.
What?
- You can't come?
- Well, it's my kid.
- The kindergarten has a class...
- Hey.
Who am I going to team up with, then?
I was really pissed partnering up
with that punk, the club president.
He'd stop me
from going anywhere I want to
and ring the bell
whenever I try to grab something.
So? Is it too big a burden
to go diving with me every week?
Am I forcing you?
No, Mr. Yoon. That's not the case.
Thanks to you,
I get to enjoy a wonderful hobby.
Yes, kid.
So just follow my footsteps, okay?
You need to get promoted to manager
this time, don't you?
You're the last one
among your recruitment peers.
Yes, you're right.
I'll try even harder.
Don't just try hard, you punk.
Do it well.
Yes, sir. I'll do it well.
Good, Native Speaker.
- Go, now.
- Yes. Goodnight, sir.
Yeah.
Mr. Min.
I heard Mr. Yoon calling you
"Native Speaker."
What does he mean by that?
Everyone in my team has been abroad
except for me.
So they say
I'm the native Korean speaker
and nicknamed me Native Speaker.
It doesn't sound like
a pleasant nickname.
Mr. Min, we saw it all.
We saw you acting
as Mr. Yoon's designated driver.
And you don't like scuba diving
yet you continue doing it
to serve him.
It's just office politics.
Everyone does this.
No, Mr. Min.
That's considered
workplace harassment.
She's right.
You should use this chance
to speak up honestly.
- Even to your wife.
- To my wife?
No, that is something I cannot do.
Your wife took this the wrong way
and thinks you're having an affair.
I'd rather live
with the misunderstanding.
Sorry?
I don't want my wife to find out
that this is
how I'm being treated at work.
Right...
I don't think
this is a matter we can let slide.
This isn't just a power dynamic.
It's gaslighting.
I can also understand why
he doesn't want his family to know.
Let's just tell his wife
that we confirmed that
he isn't having an affair.
Okay.
Also, it looks like Mr. Min
needs to be separated
from Mr. Yoon as soon as possible.
I'll try to think of a way.
This isn't something
he can handle personally.
There must be something
that the company can do.
VNow, we're home.
Time to stop thinking today.
Go home and get some rest.
You must be tired
after diving early in the morning.
Mr. Noh.
Do you want to stay for ramyeon?
That's three minutes.
Now, take a break
and have some ramyeon.
Hey, wait.
Since when did the phrase,
"Do you want to stay for ramyeon?"
come to mean, "Why don't you
eat ramyeon and work all night?"
The meaning has changed a while ago.
You didn't know?
Now, eat up.
And this isn't even actually boiled.
It's cup ramyeon.
With no kimchi or pickled radish?
Hey, you picked out good ones
in a short amount of time.
But this definition
is a bit too abstract.
You should specify
the actual relevant laws here.
It'll be more effective
to present these examples verbally.
Can you add images
and make it more visual?
Give me some time to eat ramyeon.
Isn't this example too much?
Is there anything more universal?
- What? Which one?
- This one.
Workplace harassment
always starts quietly.
It begins with a good morning
and an exchange of a glance.
Then you slowly
become excluded from the team
or get forced to do
an unreasonable amount of overtime.
Sometimes the perpetrator goes,
"You can handle that."
But other times, they go,
"Why do you do things your way?"
"Do you think work is a joke?"
What's truly scary is this.
As these instances continue
the victim begins
to blame themselves.
"Am I the weird one?"
"Am I too sensitive?"
"Do people hate me?"
THE VICTIM'S PSYCHOLOGICAL CHANGES
This kind of anxiety makes the victim
accept such absurd requests.
Everyone.
The absurd one
is always the perpetrator.
Do not doubt yourself or hesitate.
Also, do not hide but report it.
The company is obligated
to guard and protect
the valued human resources
of its workplace.
Do you understand?
- Yes.
Excuse me, Mr. Noh.
- Hello, Mr. Min.
- Hello.
Actually, I got the chance
to go to the US as an expatriate.
Congratulations.
I heard the opportunity
was originally meant for you.
I hope you didn't have to step back
because of me.
That's not something
I can just give up to someone.
You're going because you are
more than qualified for the job.
Thank you.
Also, I saw that
Mr. Yoon got disciplined.
- Is it because of me?
- Oh, no.
We confirmed an instance of him
leaving his workplace
during a business trip to go diving.
That's why he got disciplined.
So don't worry about it.
I see. Is that right?
Have fun while you work abroad.
I hope you go there
and get revitalized.
I will.
My wife is thrilled.
I'll have a good time.
Also
you two look great together.
- Sorry?
- Well...
You can notice lots of things
when you're underwater.
Even as you were diving with me
your attention and mind
were all on Ms. Joo over there.
You kept my secret
so I will keep yours, too.
Don't worry.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
Nice shot!
- You're ready to go out and play.
- Thank you, sir.
I think I can play even better,
thanks to your lessons.
Yes, right.
I looked up the case
on Haemu Pharmaceutical
and I did not get anything
during the handover.
Really? Despite all those many audits
there are no documents left behind?
Yes. By any chance,
are you more concerned
because Vice President Jeon Jae-yeol
was the previous president there?
I don't know.
Nice shot!
It's going straight to the pin!
You got it right next to the hole.
Gosh.
Man, I already said
I came to play golf.
Hey, what's up?
Really?
My sister-in-law is back?
Is it because it's been a while?
You look kind of pretty
when you sleep.
I heard you got sick.
Acute alcohol intoxication?
Didn't you tell me
to get my addiction treated?
This is freaking hilarious.
When did you return?
Dad gave me a hard time
about being abroad
while you were in this mess.
Anyway, what happened?
I'm sure it wasn't because
you missed me so much.
Were you that pissed
about your brother becoming
co-vice president?
Are you serious?
What is this? You're boring.
Hyun-young.
Yes?
Let's call it quits.
What?
Let's get divorced.
What is this nonsense?
Why should we get divorced?
You're unhappy with me too.
It's time to free each other.
Let me know when you've decided.
We can discuss the rest
through our lawyers.
Hey, you have to tell me the reason.
You and I didn't get married
to be happy, anyway.
Why are you suddenly doing this?
Have you finally lost it
just like your mom?
I no longer want to live like this.
You know you have
zero chance at becoming the successor
if you divorce me, right?
Hyun-young.
I'll manage my own life.
So please
just divorce me.
Hey, my husband is acting weird.
Can you do some digging?
When do you get off work?
Come to my place for dinner.
JOO IN-A
Why? Are you telling me
to stop by for ramyeon again?
Today is the real deal.
Great work today, everyone.
- Great work today.
What was that?
I think Ms. Joo just winked at me.
- What?
- You must've seen something weird.
Or she must've squinted
because she had something in her eye.
No, I'm serious.
- She did this.
- Do you think
this is a sign of some sort?
For what? Like, "You are sealed
for overtime tomorrow"?
Her eyes must've stung.
Stop talking nonsense. All right.
We never got a chance to have
a proper team dinner
after Mr. Noh got discharged.
Why don't we go out
and eat something delicious?
- Okay.
- I'd love to.
Ms. Yoon?
Well, it depends on what we eat.
Oh, my.
I can't believe she's saying that.
We need to eat
something really good today, then.
It's been a while, so I'll let us use
the corporate card!
- All right!
- Are we unleashing the company card?
That means we have to go.
- Let's go.
- Wait.
I'm so sorry, but today...
I really want to go, too.
But I have an important appointment.
I see.
It's okay. We can work overtime.
- Yes.
- Me too.
- Overtime it is, then.
- It is.
Let's see.
Oh, my. What brings you
to the 14th floor, Ms. Park?
I had to deliver something
to the Planning Team.
Is that so?
You must be enjoying yourself...
caught between two men.
Among the two men
exactly which one
are you furious about?
If I tell you,
will you let me have one of them?
In that case,
it doesn't have to be Ki-jun.
There's no need to do that.
You two will be over shortly.
That's how he handles
all his romantic relationships.
Very casual.
Let's say
I back down from Jeon Jae-yeol.
Can you even have him, A-jeong?
I get that you're upset because of me
but try not to cross the line.
I may look quite young
but I am an executive member
of this company.
Executive Assistant Park A-jeong.
Excuse me.
- The White Blood Cell show!
Go.
Hey, how do you do that?
Open up your throat
and throw it in.
Give me just a little bit of time.
I'll be there soon
after I humor them.
That's so amazing.
- I mean, how do you do this?
- It's not a big deal.
- You could even do an eating show.
- He could.
Why won't the meat get cooked?
Is the heat too weak?
No, it's the highest.
It's taking a while
because the cut is so thick.
Give me that. I'll do it.
- No, I'll do it.
- It's okay. I'm on a diet, anyway.
- I'll do it.
- No, I...
- Give me that too.
- Goodness.
All right! Eat your meat! Hurry!
- All right!
- I'd love to!
Eat up your meat!
- I will.
- All right.
Thanks.
Do you not need
a toothbrush and a razor?
- What?
- Aren't you having a hot night?
You have to grab a toothbrush
for your partner.
It's been so long for me.
Where can I find one?
Can you drink more?
- Yes.
- I get drunk really easily.
- But...
- All right, everyone. Your glasses.
Let's make a toast! Cheers!
- Cheers!
- Drink up.
- You can take your alcohol.
- Why don't you have another drink?
- Shall we?
Okay. We're partying
until we drop and die tonight.
- Cheers!
- Chug your drink!
- Yes!
- Okay.
- Who needs a drink?
Now, another toast!
- Cheers.
- It's the last one.
- The last one.
- The last one!
- It's the last drink here!
- Hey!
That was so good.
Where are we going for round two?
- A karaoke room.
- Let's go karaokeing.
- Mr. Noh. Where's Mr. Noh?
- Yes!
- Hey!
- Come back.
- You can't run away.
- Get back here.
You can't leave today.
- Not today.
- You're the hero tonight.
Drunk as a fish
I am dead drunk
I have fallen
For the scent of your love
I have fallen!
Oh, oh, oh
- All right!
- Sing it!
My goodness.
- Hello?
- Okay!
I'm sorry.
They're holding me back
like today is my last day on earth.
I'm so sorry.
I think it'll take
just a little longer.
Is that so?
Well, I can't help it.
Team dinners are a part of work,
so make sure you stay until the end.
At least he won't be hungry.
That means I'll have to eat
which means my tummy will stick out.
But what can I do?
What?
He said he'd be late.
What is this? A surprise?
You're here already?
- Hey! I'm feeling too great!
- No.
- Just one more bottle.
- Oh, no.
Drunk as a fish
Goodbye!
- Goodbye!
- Boys!
- I'm feeling too great.
- Bye, now.
Time to go!
Come on, man. One more bottle.
- Now.
- All right. I get it.
Okay, then.
Mr. Noh, let's grab
just one more drink.
- Great. I just need one more drink.
- Awesome.
- No.
- What?
That's all for today.
Maybe next time, okay?
- There is no next time.
- There's only today.
- No.
- Where are you going?
- Mr. Noh!
- Just one more drink!
- Don't go!
You must've been expecting someone.
Yes, I don't know why you're here
but I want you to keep it short
and leave.
I may sound like an idiot
but even as I married
someone who wasn't you
I never once had thought
I had lost you.
That's a selfish thought.
You said you'd be on my side.
I think I lived my life
depending on those words.
You said you were
honoring your words.
I don't care what it is.
I'm getting a divorce.
I told my wife, too.
What do you think you're doing?
What kind of response
did you expect from me?
"Wow, Jae-yeol is divorcing!
I'm going to date him now!"
- Did you think I'd say that?
- I know
I can't get you back
even if I get divorced.
I know
I've lost you for good.
But no matter what I do,
I couldn't let my feelings go.
The least I can do
is be honest with my feelings.
That's why I'm divorcing.
It's not because of you
but because of me.
It's killing me.
I regret everything, In-a.
I'm sorry.
I got here too late, didn't I?
The one
you had been waiting for is here.
I'm done talking, so excuse me.
Wow, you prepared a lot of things.
Did you make the pasta yourself?
It looks great.
I got these delivered.
Good call. Delivery food is the best.
Haemu Group's Head of Audit
couldn't have had any time to cook.
You need to use all your free time
to stare at my face.
Aren't you going to ask?
You're in a foul mood.
And you must be curious.
Stop beating around the bush
and just ask me.
I do want to know.
And yes, I'm in a foul mood.
But I
do not want to make myself ask.
It's probably something
between you two.
I guess today isn't a good day.
And you prepared so much.
Don't drink, and go to sleep early.
You have to be at work tomorrow.
Okay?
I'll get going now.
Don't go.
Stay by my side.
Joo In-a...
What on earth is she to you?
She's someone I would die with.
Can you even give up everything
for that woman?
If I must.
Let's say
I back down from Jeon Jae-yeol.
Can you even have him, A-jeong?
My gosh. We almost ran late.
And I'm never late to work.
And I never wear the same tie
two days in a row.
That's the thing about dating.
New definitions are introduced
to your dictionary.
You're a smooth talker.
But I can't accept being late.
Have another great day.
- You too.
- Thanks.
Good morning.
- Good morning.
SENT BY NONAME
REPORTING MS. JOO IN-A
- What?
- What is this?
Did you see it?
I'd like to report
on Ms. Joo In-a's private life.
Ms. Joo In-a remains aloof
while keeping an eye on others
and punishing them
but she's actually a hypocrite
who lives
a very complicated private life.
I attach
a picture of Ms. Joo In-a
with her superior, who is married.
FILING FOR LOVE
Is the rumor about Ms. Joo true?
So who's the man in the photo
that you exchanged greetings with?
I know he's the vice president,
this feels way out of...
Don't frown. You'll get wrinkles.
I'll be an iron fortress! Let's go!
Are you crying?
You know, Ms. Joo's mail...
The sender's location was traced
to Mr. Noh Ki-jun's home.
Are you going to save me
like a knight in shining armor?
Just say I did it.
Mr. Noh Ki-jun will face
disciplinary action.
I'll take responsibility.
Subtitles by Eunsook Youn
and Jennifer Lim